For this build, I will pick around three
to five images that in my opinion enough
to give the workflow a clear signal
without making it too messy. Once I have
them, I save everything into one folder
and bring it into the face merge
workflow. This is the workflow. You can
see that I have two branches here. The
top branch is for Nano Banana and the
bottom branch is for Chat GPT image
tool. For this build, I'm using image
tool. That's the new image model from
Open AI. I still use Nano Banana tool
and Nano Banana Pro. They are still good
models in my eyes, but after a lot of
generations, image tool gives me a
slightly more realistic look when it
comes to generate faces and details for
this specific